我和我的兄弟姊妹是历史上
最早的吸血鬼
ELlJAH: My siblings and I
are the first vampires in history.
是真祖家族
The Originals.
三百年前，我们帮助建立了纽奥良
这个城市
Three hundred years ago,
we helped to build the city of New Orleans.
我们一家人曾经在这里
We were happy here.
很快乐
A family.
最近，一群女巫把我弟弟引诱回来
Recently, a coven of
witches lured my brother back,
利用他未出生的孩子做筹码
using his unborn child as leverage.
我试图帮他
但他却把我出卖给了他的敌人
ELlJAH: I tried to help him,
but he betrayed me to his enemy,
吸血鬼马赛尔
the vampire Marcel.
从那时起，我被一个强大的女巫掌控着
Since then, I've been held
prisoner by a powerful witch.
我弟弟试图操纵他人来解救我
My brother seeks to manipulate others
to procure my release.
但我有自己的计划
But I have my own plan.
如果这个女巫真的是敌人
If this witch proves to be an enemy,
我会不惜一切代价阻止她
I will stop her by whatever
means necessary.
他们都说你是可敬的
You're the one they call honorable.
是的
Yes.
他们是这么说我的
That's what they call me.
然而我跟随我弟弟来到这里
来到纽奥良参与战争
And yet I followed my brother here
to New Orleans to engage in a war.
那么
So...
我问你
...I ask you...
你觉得这听起来可敬吗？
...does that sound honorable to you?
你脸色不太好
You don't look well.
要不是今天早上
我的胸口里还插着一把神秘的匕首
Well, only this morning, I had a
mystical dagger embedded in my chest.
我得说我还是相当把持得住的
So, I'd say I'm holding
myself together quite well.
黛维娜，我相信你和我有能力
在女巫和吸血鬼的战争开始之前
Davina, I believe that you and l
have the power to end a war between
就终止这一切
witches and vampires
before it truly begins.
我会管好我的弟弟
你就做好你自己
I, by keeping my brother in line.
You, by behaving as your true self,
而不是马赛尔或女巫的工具
not some tool for Marcel
or the witches.
我凭什么相信你？
And why should I trust you?
首先，尽管我饥肠辘辘
Well, for one thing,
in spite of a ravenous hunger,
我也没有试图要吸你的血
I have not tried to take your blood.
为什么不呢？这里就只有我
And why not?
I'm the only one here.
即使是现在这样的状态
我也不会去吸一个孩子的血
Even in my present condition,
I would not feed from a child.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：罪人与圣人
主演：约瑟夫摩根
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
主演：克莱儿荷特
我们说好的
KLAUS: We had a deal.
你保护我未出生的孩子
主演：菲比托金
You protect my unborn child,
我瓦解马赛尔的军队
主演：菲比托金
I dismantle Marcel's army.
在我一直忙着做好我该做的事情时
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
And whilst I've been busy
fulfilling my part of the bargain,
你让海莉受到了攻击
you allowed Hayley to be attacked
差点被一群疯女巫杀死
主演：丹妮耶拉皮纳达
and almost killed
差点被一群疯女巫杀死
by a gaggle of lunatic witches.
这与我毫无关系，我发誓
I had nothing to do with it, I swear.
我和海莉是连结在一起的，记得吗？
Hayley and I are linked, remember?
她死，我也会死
She dies, I die.
那么那些人是谁？
Then who were they?
他们是一小群极端份子
They're a faction of extremists.
莎宾愚蠢地告诉了他们
主演：莉雅派普斯
Sabine stupidly told them about
她看到的这个孩子的一些幻象
some vision she had about the baby.
什么幻象？
What kind of vision?
她总能看到幻象，绝对是可以解读的
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
She has them all the time.
They're totally open
to interpretation.
我猜这次她错了
I'm guessing she's wrong on this one.
容我问一句，这个特别的幻象
她是如何解读？
Well, how, may I ask,
was this particular vision interpreted?
大致就是你的孩子
将导致所有女巫死亡
Pretty much that your baby
would bring death to all witches.
我突然更加喜欢这个孩子了
Ah, well, I grow fonder of
this child by the second.
苏菲，听着我向以利亚保证过
制片：兰斯安德森
Sophie, look. I promised Elijah
that I would protect the Mikaelson
我会保护米卡森家的奇迹之子
同时他会试图获得女巫黛维娜的忠诚
miracle baby whilst he tries to win,
your witch, Davina's loyalty.
不如你告诉我
这一小群人有多极端呢？
Why don't you tell me just
how extreme this faction is?
以利亚在和黛维娜谈？
制片：朗恩麦克劳德
Elijah's talking to Davina?
对，就在我们说话这时，我想是
Yeah, as we speak, I imagine.
我想她对那一小群人会有许多要说的
I'm guessing she'll have
plenty to say about that crowd.
请说吧
Do tell.
我并非一直都是女巫的支持者
I wasn't always an advocate
for the witches.
（八个月前）
喝光吧，各位
Whoo!
Drink up, everybody!
他们在里约就是这样开派对的
This is how they party in Rio!
我姊姊像我父母那样献身于女巫
My sister was
devoted like our parents,
我们的教育非常严格
编剧：玛格丽特麦金泰尔
and our upbringing was very strict,
快把我逼疯了
编剧：茱莉普烈克
which drove me nuts.
我一到21岁
就离开法语区旅行，放纵
The minute I turned 21,
I left the Quarter to travel and play.
但我想做个厨师
导演：克里斯葛瑞斯莫
But I wanted to be a chef,
所以我回到了卢梭酒吧
导演：克里斯葛瑞斯莫
so I came back to Rousseau's.
简安
Oh! Jane-Anne!
嘿
Hey!
刚刚那个不是我
That wasn't me.
嗨
Hi!
哦
Oh!
欢迎回家，苏菲
Welcome home, Soph.
我们能去别处聊聊吗？
Can we go someplace to talk?
说吧
Just tell me.
长老们要求举行投票
The elders called a vote.
我们正在筹划收获祭
We're moving
forward with the Harvest.
什么？
What?
收获祭是什么鬼东西？
What the bloody hell is the Harvest?
是我们女巫每三百年就会做一次的仪式
那样我们与祖先的魔法
It's a ritual our coven does every
three centuries so that the bond
会重新恢复联系
to our ancestral magic is restored.
我们安抚我们的祖先
他们就会让我们祖传的力量得以延续
We appease our ancestors, they keep
our ancestral power flowing.
我怎么没听说过？
And why haven't I heard of this?
因为收获祭总是被认为是神话
Because the Harvest
always seemed like a myth,
一代代传下来的故事
a story passed down
through generations.
就像诺亚方舟或是佛陀在水上行走
Like Noah's ark or the
Buddha walking on water.
有些人真的相信
The kind some people take literally,
有些却不信
and some people don't.
如欲重生，必先牺牲
To be reborn, we must sacrifice.
如欲重生，必有信仰
To be reborn, we must have faith.
你相信收获祭吗？
Do you have faith in the Harvest?
一点也不信
Not for a second!
苏菲
一嘘
-Sophie.
-Shh.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
拯救你放弃的团体
Saving the community you renounced.
你们都太荒谬了
You're all ridiculous!
莫妮克？不是吧？
Monique? Seriously?
我妈妈告诉我我必须这么做
My mom told me I had to.
是啊，那我要跟你妈妈谈谈了
Yeah. Well, your mom and l
are gonna have words.
她们让一些女孩准备了几个月
SOPHlE: They had the girls of our
community preparing for months.
会有四个被选中用来献祭
Four would be chosen for the Harvest.
她们说那是一种荣誉
她们很特别
They said that it was an honor,
that they were special.
我觉得那只是个神话
I thought it was a myth.
那是吗？
Was it?
马赛尔
Marcel.
这个时间对你来说有点早了吧？
Bit early in the day for you, isn't it?
我知道，我让一切看起来很简单
但我还是有一个帝国要管理
I know. I make this look easy,
but I still have an empire to run.
幸好是你不是我
Rather you than me.
那些职责似乎很让人厌烦呢
All that responsibility
seems like such a bore.
有件事你应该会感兴趣
Well, this might spice things up.
我刚听说在河口有一群死掉的巫师
I just heard about a bunch of dead
witches out in the bayou.
似乎是狼人干的
只不过昨天不是满月
The kind of damage a werewolf might do,
only there was no full moon.
我得去见一个线人
I have an informant out
there I need to meet,
我很希望你能陪我去
and I would love for you
to go with me.
河口死掉的巫师
Dead witches in the bayou.
听起来不算是什么麻烦
更像是值得庆祝的事情
Sounds like less of a problem and
more like a cause for celebration.
有东西杀了他们
也许还在某处
Well, something killed them
and may still be out there,
而你的血是治愈狼人咬伤的唯一办法
and with your blood the
only cure for a werewolf bite....
我很希望你陪我走一趟
I would love for you to accompany me.
为什么不呢？
我很久没去河口了
Well, why not?
I haven't been to the bayou in ages.
这就来
I'm on my way.
再见，兄弟
Peace out, brother.
就是这个
This is the one.
你现在不能出去
SOPHlE: You can't go out there now.
我得聚集巫师的遗体，把他们献祭
I need to gather the witches'
remains and consecrate them.
如果在日落前没做到
If I don't get to
them before sundown,
我们就会失去与他们魔法的联系
we lose the link to their magic.
那些巫师试图杀死海莉
Those witches tried to kill Hayley.
我希望马赛尔的线人
找不到任何会将他
I prefer for Marcel's informant not
to find anything that would lead him
指引到我们、她，或者
你知道的，那个
back to us, to her,
or to, you know, that.
你们都是一类人
You are all class.
乖乖待着，等我回来再继续你的故事
Stay put and save the rest
of your story 'til I return.
瞧瞧谁回来了
Look who's back.
来探望你关在阁楼的囚犯吗？
Here to visit your
prisoner in the attic?
歇歇吧
她不是囚犯
Lay off.
She's not a prisoner.
我今晚就会带她离开这里
太多人知道她在哪了
And I'm moving her tonight.
Too many people know where she is.
自从我离开之后
I've been hearing about
what you've been up to
就一直听闻你的事
since I've been out of town.
利用那个女孩阻止女巫使用魔法？
Using that girl to keep
the witches from doing magic?
无意冒犯，基神父
如果你打算维护女巫的权利
All respect, Father K. If you're
gonna defend the witches' rights,
我们就没什么好说的了
we got nothing to talk about.
你拉小提琴？
Do you play?
那个…不是我的
That's not mine.
好消息，小黛
Good news, little D.
我要带你离开这个满是灰尘的地方
I'm moving you out
of this pile of dust.
真的吗？什么时候？
Are you serious? When?
今晚
我只需再做些准备
Tonight. I just need to lock in
the arrangements.
我们的真祖怎么样了？
How's our Original?
别动他
Don't disturb the body.
我正在施咒呢
I have a spell in progress.
好吧
快点收拾，只带你想带的
I bet you do. Pack up, okay?
Only what you wanna take.
其他需要的东西我会再买给你
I'll buy you anything else you need.
好
Okay.
你没告诉他我已经醒了
You didn't reveal that I was awake.
我们还没聊完呢
We're not done talking yet.
你和马赛尔看起来很亲密
You and Marcel seem very close.
马赛尔是我的家人
Marcel is my family.
但马赛尔却喜欢伤害女巫
And yet Marcel is someone who
delights in harming the witches.
我觉得那些人才是你该认为是家人的人
Those people, I would think,
you would consider family.
这不让你困扰吗？
This doesn't trouble you?
不
No.
她们活该
They deserve it.
你为什么那么说？
Why would you say that?
因为她们是骗子，全都是
'Cause they're liars, all of them.
她们让我和我朋友做这个收获祭仪式
They made me and my friends
do this Harvest ritual.
她们说我们的参与
会为我们的家人带来力量，健康
They said our participation would
bring our family strength, health.
我们会永远被尊为
这群女巫的救世主
That we'd forever be celebrated
as saviors of the community.
但她们真正想要的只是更多的力量
But all they really
wanted was more power.
所以我在她们得手前就离开了
So, I left before they could get it.
现在她们就快没时间了
因为收获祭之后
And now they're running out of time
because after the Harvest
就是收割
如果她们不能完成仪式
comes the Reaping.
And if they don't complete the Harvest,
就不会有收割
there won't be a Reaping.
很快，法语区所有的女巫
就会开始失去她们的力量
Soon, all the witches in the Quarter
will start to lose their power.
最后，她们将不再是女巫了
Eventually, they'll cease
to be witches altogether.
那要如何才能完成这个仪式呢？
So what does it take
to complete this ritual?
我必须死
I have to die.
嘿，搞什么？
Hey. What the hell?
你反正是要出去的，不是吗？
You're going out
there anyway, aren't you?
我想和你一起走
I wanna go with you.
不，谢了
今天早上已经被克劳斯威胁过了
No thanks. Already got assaulted
by Klaus this morning.
不想再来一次
Don't need a repeat.
如果那个害死那些巫师的东西
What if whatever is responsible
for all those dead witches
还在外面呢？
is still out there?
我们已经确定那家伙喜欢我
讨厌女巫
We've already established that
it likes me and hates witches.
所以你和我在一起会更安全
So you'll be safer with me.
抱歉，我可不信你会突然关心我的安全
Sorry if I'm not buying your
sudden concern for my safety.
听着
我一开始来到这个破城市的原因
Listen. The whole reason I came to
this stupid town in the first place
就是为了多了解我的家人
was to learn more about my family.
是你姊姊告诉我
马赛尔把所有狼人
Your sister is the one that told me
Marcel ran the werewolves
从法语区赶到了河口
而昨晚
out of the Quarter into the bayou.
And last night,
我很确定是某个狼人守护天使救了我
pretty sure that some
guardian angel wolf saved my life.
所以我要和你一起去
So I'm coming with you.
你们俩能再傻一点吗？
Could you two be more idiotic?
两个人够玩追踪游戏了
Two can play the follow game,
you know?
你们听到克劳斯的话了
他和马赛尔正在去你们要去的地方
You heard Klaus. He and Marcel are
heading right where you're going.
那就分散他们的注意力
除非你想把一个
So distract them. Because
unless you wanna lock a hormonal,
荷尔蒙过剩的怀孕狼人关在墓穴里
我和你一起去
pregnant werewolf in a tomb,
I'm coming with you.
如果以利亚听到我和宝宝
因为窒息而死
And wouldn't Elijah be mad
if he hears that the baby and l
不知道他会不会很生气？
died of asphyxiation?
怎么了，蕾贝卡？
我和你前男友出去你生气了吗？
What's the matter, Rebekah?
You cross that I'm out with your ex?
怎么回事，你那边吵死了
What is all that dreadful
hillbilly ruckus in the background?
从这该死的招牌来看
这里是大奥吉河口酒吧
According to the dreadful signage,
it's Big Auggie's Bayou Bar.
多点几杯威士忌酒
Well, order up a few rounds
of moonshine
暂时离死掉的巫师远点
and stay clear of the
dead witches for a few.
那女巫在执行葬礼任务
你孩子的妈正享受精神探索
The witch is on a burial mission,
your baby mama is on a spirit quest,
而我要连守以利亚的约定保证她的安全
and I'm keeping Elijah's
promise to keep her safe.
所以拜托你拖一拖
So stall, please.
没事吧？
Everything okay?
一如既往
Just the usual.
喜怒无常的妹妹啊
Temperamental sister.
你的线人呢？
So, where's your informant?
汤玛斯？他现在在外面四处打探呢
Tomas?
He's out sniffing around.
来杯酒，然后我们再找他
Grab a drink,
then we'll chase him down.
我想这是我们聊聊的好机会
Well, I suppose it will give us
a chance to talk things over,
比如你为什么还不把以利亚还给我
Iike why you haven't returned Elijah.
也许你的小女巫
越来越喜欢他的陪伴了
Maybe your young witch
has grown partial to his company.
她一定是太无聊了
She must get so bored.
你就是不放弃，是吗？
You never stop, do you?
你就是不回答，是吗？
You never answer, do you?
你为什么对黛维娜那么好奇？
Why are you so curious about Davina?
如果我有一个16岁的强大女巫
对我言听计从
If I had a 16-year-old all-powerful
witch at my beck and call,
你也会对她很好奇的
you would wonder about her too.
你绝不会得到她的
You're never gonna get her.
好吧
Okay.
那我问个无关紧要的问题吧
I'll ask the
harmless questions, then.
你怎么认识她的？
How did you meet her?
这也许会让你惊讶
That might surprise you.
八个月前
就在我禁止女巫使用魔法前
This was eight months ago, before
I banned the witches from using magic.
吸血鬼和女巫的关系
Relations between vampires and witches
不管怎样，虽然算不上
所谓的友好
weren't what you'd call friendly,
by any means.
但这么说吧
我们也没那么多分歧
But let's just say,
we were a little less divided.
事实上，我们一些人还相处得蛮好
In fact, some of us were
getting along just fine.
完蛋了
It's so screwed up.
我要面对精神失常的激进女巫
I'm dealing with whacked out,
militant witches.
在你看来，所有女巫都有点疯在
Hey, you witches all
got a little crazy in you.
我姊姊这次真的是太极端了
And my sister's really
gone off the deep end this time.
是啊，简安就是极端的殉道者
Yeah. Jane-Anne has got
martyr written all over her.
这是肯定的
That's for sure.
我们当中所有16岁女孩都在她们手上
她们都想成为那场
They've got every 16-year-old girl
in our coven dying to be one of the four
荒诞仪式上的那四个祭品之一
chosen for this crazy-ass ritual.
要我帮忙吗？
Anything I can do to help?
不要，你和她们的过节已经够多了
No. You've caused enough
trouble with them.
我哪有那么厉害？
What, little, old me?
你这个浑球
You're a dick.
你总是和女巫挑起事端
You always stir it
up with the witches,
这就是为什么这件事…
which is why this...
只有你我知道即可
...stays between us.
你和苏菲有一腿
KLAUS: You and Sophie.
你这伪君子
You hypocrite.
你折磨那些女巫，而自己却和
You torture those witches,
and yet there you are,
苏菲德弗罗玩着
罗密欧与朱丽叶的浪漫戏码
getting positively Romeo and Juliet
with Sophie Deveraux.
可不能这么说
It wasn't like that.
这是一个各取所需的男女关系
It was a mutually satisfying hookup.
这么说苏菲在她最需要的时候
没找你这个
So, if Sophie didn't turn to you,
her secret vampire lover,
地下吸血鬼情人帮忙
那她怎么做的？
in her hour of need,
what did she do?
她做了所有好女孩都会做的事
She did what any good girl would do.
她去找了她的神父
She went to her priest.
你从不关心女巫的事，苏菲
WOMAN: You've never cared
about witch business, Sophie,
而你现在竟好意思把我们的
秘密行动透露给外人
and now you have the gall to reveal
our private dealings to an outsider.
你得另辟蹊径了
You have to find another way.
你觉得我们做这些容易吗？
You think we do this lightly?
法语区的吸血鬼势力越渐壮大
The vampire presence in the
Quarter is growing stronger.
我们需要更大的力量去抵御他们
We need more power to fight them off.
艰难的时期要有强硬的对策
Harsh times call for harsh measures.
这不仅仅是强硬了，贝丝蒂娜
This is a little more
than harsh, Bastianna.
你不理解是因为你不相信
You don't understand
because you don't believe.
你从未相信过
You've never believed.
但是我相信，我愿为此孤注一掷
But I believe enough to put
everything on the line for this.
被选中为祭品
是种荣耀
And being chosen for the offering,
it's an honor.
是个谬论，简安
It's a myth, Jane-Anne.
你们的所作所为不仅是错的
What you are planning
to do is not only wrong,
在这个城市里，还是违法的
in my city, it's illegal.
在这个吸血鬼横行的城市吗？
In your city full of vampires?
这里的吸血鬼和人类已经达成共识
The vampires and the human faction
have an arrangement,
就像我们和你们之间一样
just like we have with you all.
保护当地百姓，保护家园
Protect the locals,
protect our homes,
我们选择了另一种方式
we look the other way.
而你们的做法太激进了
What you are planning goes too far.
我们只是要回我们需要的
We are simply taking what we need.
我们和祖先的联系日益减弱
Our connection to our
ancestors weakens over time.
一分耕耘一分收获
收获祭就是这样
You sow, and you reap.
That's the way the Harvest works.
我是你们女巫在这个城市唯一的朋友
I am the only ally you witches
have in this town.
你们真的想孤军对抗马赛尔吗？
Do you really wanna face
Marcel without me?
因为如果你们执意要举行收获祭
Because that is what
you'll be dealing with
就会面临这个问题
if you go through with the Harvest.
没事吧，基兰叔叔？
Everything okay in here, Uncle Kieran?
我们刚说完，西恩
We were just finishing, Sean.
是吧？
Right?
我想我已经把话说清楚了
I believe I've made myself clear.
我们会把这个问题交给长老处理
We'll take this matter to the elders.
继续学习，西恩
Continue to study, Sean.
你的叔叔是个很好的榜样
Your uncle is an excellent role model.
女巫们对基兰很生气
MARCEL: The witches
were furious with Kieran.
苏菲告诉我女巫对他的侄子西恩下了咒
Sophie tells me that the witches
put a hex on his nephew, Sean.
使他逐渐丧失理智
Made it seem like
he was slowly losing his mind,
以分散基兰的注意力
好让她们继续准备仪式
in order to distract Kieran
while they kept planning for the Harvest.
也就是说她们对基兰的侄子下手
So they attacked Kieran's nephew.
对
Yeah.
那孩子之后就变了
变得很暴力
Kid wasn't the same after that.
Ended up going postal,
杀了他神学院所有的同学
killing all his
fellow seminary students,
所有人，最后自杀了
all of them, and then himself.
我好像在哪看到过
I might have read about that.
那孩子杀了一个双胞胎
还是他就是双胞胎之一或什么的
The boy killed a twin,
or he was a twin or something.
不不，他们说他有个双胞胎妹妹
Oh, no, no.
They said that he had a twin sister.
告诉我
So, enlighten me.
你说你必须死是什么意思？
What did you mean
when you said you had to die?
收获祭就是这样
That's what the Harvest was.
她们说要把我们四个女孩置于一种
They said they'd put us
four girls in a state of, like,
安宁的状态，作为祭品
peaceful limbo as part
of the offering,
之复我们将在收割时
苏醒并重生
and then later at the Reaping,
we'd awaken and be reborn.
我没到达那个状态
I never got as far as the limbo part,
也就是说仪式没有完成
which means the Harvest
isn't complete.
这也就是女巫们很生气的原因
That's why the witches
are so freaked out.
收割的期限就要到了
The Reaping is just around the corner,
如果在此之前没有完成，就都结束了
and if they don't finish it before then,
it's over.
我要做的就是耐心等待
All I have to do is wait it out.
然后呢？
And then what?
她们会受到惩罚，我就解脱了
They're punished, and I'm free.
从马赛尔的禁锢中解脱吗？
From Marcel?
从魔法的禁锢
Of magic.
我们的法力都会逐渐消逝
All our power will drain away.
我会变成普通人
I'll be normal.
这是你想要的吗，变成普通人？
And is that what you want,
to be normal?
我只是不想像现在这样
I just don't wanna be what I am.
我有时控制不了，魔法
I can't control it sometimes,
the magic.
我会伤害别人
即使我不是故意的
I hurt people,
even when I don't mean to.
和我说说你的朋友吧
Why don't you tell me
about your friends?
你一定很想他们
You must miss them.
有个叫提姆的
There's Tim.
他对女巫的事一无所知
他是个普通人
He doesn't know about any
of this witch stuff. He's normal.
我最好的朋友莫妮克
My best friend, Monique.
她也是收获祭中的祭品之一
She was a part of the Harvest too.
她很幸运
She's lucky.
没人为保护我而战，却有人为她而战
No one ever fought for me,
but someone fought for her.
唯一一个敢于抵制收获祭仪式的
The only one who ever spoke out
against the Harvest
就是莫妮克的阿姨
was Monique's aunt.
她是谁？
And who is that?
苏菲德弗罗
Sophie Deveraux.
这个收获祭什么的，跟我多说些
So this Harvest thingy, tell me more.
克劳斯说要等他
Klaus said to wait.
对，他还说要远离河口
Yes. He also said to
stay out of the bayou,
但我们却在这些烦人的生物中穿梭
让人浑身发毛
and yet here we are amongst
the crawly, buzzy creatures.
我们到了
We're here.
哇
Whoa.
那是狼人的爪印吗？
Is that a wolf track?
谁在那里？
Who's there?
搞什么？
What the hell?
是真祖吗？
An Original?
让我消化一下
Let me understand this.
你和海莉没头没脑地闯进了河口
Against all logic,
you and Hayley went to the Bayou,
在那碰上一个可能是马赛尔线人的人
where you ran into a man you
think may be Marcel's informant,
然后你们却让他逃了
and then you lost him.
对，既然我们得出了结论
我作为妹妹、朋友
Yes, and now that we've established
that I am a failure as a sister
和真祖都很失败
你大概要知道
and a friend and an Original,
you should probably know
他正要去向马赛尔通风报信
he's on his way to Marcel
right now to rat me out.
骨瘦如柴，神色慌张
像见鬼了一样
Skinny guy in a hurry,
looks like he saw a ghost?
我来处理
I'll handle it.
但我还需要有人让马赛尔分心
But I'll need a distraction.
我这就来
I'm on my way.
又是你妹妹打的吗？
Your sister again?
她渴望得到关注
She craves attention.
我们继续聊
So, come along.
你快说到精彩之处了
You were just
getting to the juicy bits.
我不随便拿这件事开玩笑的
I can't joke around about this.
虽然那时我干了很多事
但我是不会对小孩下手的
I've done a lot in my day,
but I do have a rule about kids.
除了苏菲，从未有人质疑收获祭
No one but Sophie ever
questioned the Harvest...
包括我的亲生母亲
...not even my own mother.
所以我也没怀疑
So, neither did l.
我们认为这是无上光荣
We thought it was such an honor.
我们深信不疑
We had such faith.
我们太傻了
We were so stupid.
仪式怎么开始的？
So, how did it begin?
我们像公主一样被带出来
We were led out like princesses.
我母亲十分骄傲
My mother was so proud.
我们的法力
终将随着与祖先联系的减弱而消亡
Our magic fades as our ties
to our ancestors weaken over time.
我们恳请他们接受祭品
以示吾等之信仰
We beseech them, accept this
offering as a sign of our faith.
贝丝蒂娜，长老之一
召唤四大元素
Bastianna, one of the elders
called upon the four elements
将我们过去和未来的法力结合在一起
to bind our past and future
magic together.
以土连结祖先
Earth to connect us to our ancestors.
以水净化众女巫
Water to heal the community.
以风将我们送达祖先那并归来
Wind to carry us
to our ancestors and back.
以火涤清罪恶
Fire to purify.
在我们准备就绪后
我们很清楚接下来的事
After all our preparation,
we knew exactly what to expect.
几周以来，她们告诉我们
扎伤我们手掌的刀子
For weeks, they told us that the magic
in the knife they used to cut our palms
其魔法会使我们入睡
随后在收割时
would put us to sleep
and that later at the Reaping,
我们都将复活
we would all be resurrected.
她们说我们会苏醒并团聚
拥有无边法力
They said we'd awaken and all be
together and more powerful than ever.
就像我们排练的一样
And it was just like we rehearsed it.
只要扎一下我们的手掌
All that was left was just
a little cut on our palms
完成血祭
for the blood sacrifice.
不要，住手，贝丝蒂娜，住手
No! Stop! Bastianna, stop!
你快住手，贝丝蒂娜，别这么做
You have to stop.
Bastianna, please don't do this.
即便苏菲竭力阻止
我们也没有怀疑
DAVINA; Even after Sophie tried to
stop it, we didn't suspect anything.
如欲重生，必先牺牲
To be born, you must sacrifice.
你相信吗？
Do you have faith?
天啊
(ALL SCREAMlNG)
Oh, my God!
拜托不要
Please stop!
参加仪式的每个人
都知道会发生这种事
Everyone involved in the ritual
knew that this would happen.
除了我们四个
Except the four of us.
她们不是要我们入睡
她们要杀了我们
They weren't putting us to sleep.
They were slaughtering us.
不，不要
(SOBBlNG)
No, no!
莫妮克德弗罗
Monique Deveraux.
不要！不要！
No! No!
不要去，莫妮克！
Don't go, Monique!
我向周围的人求救
但连我的亲生母亲都置我于不顾
I begged for someone to help.
My own mother turned away from me.
求求你们，不要
Don't do this! Please!
苏菲疯狂地尖叫着，乞求她姊姊
或是任何人做点什么
Sophie screamed and screamed for
her sister, anyone to do something.
不要杀她
你们疯了吗？
Don't kill her!
What is wrong with you?
但所有人都无动于衷
But no one did.
但你还是活下来了
Yet you survived.
一定有什么阻止了事情的发生
Therefore, someone or
something intervened.
是的
Yes.
终于有人来救我们了
Someone finally did.
莫妮克，快跑
快跑
Monique, run away!
Run away.
马赛尔
Marcel!
是你阻止了那一切
You're the one who stopped it.
基兰从苏菲那得知了一切
Kieran knew every detail from Sophie.
自从他侄子在教堂大屠杀后
After his nephew's
massacre in the church,
他悲痛欲绝
他在收获祭之前离开了这里
he was so torn up,
he left town just before the Harvest,
但走之前，他来找我
要我去阻止收获祭
but on his way out, he came to me,
and he asked me to stop the Harvest.
他知道我不希望女巫们变得更强
He knew I didn't want the witches
getting any more power...
而我也最见不得欺负小孩的人
...and I do have a rule
about people abusing kids.
所以我照做了
但我还是迟了一步
So, I did what he asked,
but I was too late.
不要，莫妮克，不要
No! Monique, no!
放开我！
住手！住手！
Let go of me!
Stop it!
放开我！
住手！
Let go of me!
Stop it!
有我在
I got you.
看到黛维娜反抗我有种说不上来的感觉
There was something
about seeing Davina fighting.
她没有轻易屈服于这场屠杀，你懂吗？
She didn't just go along
to the slaughter, you know?
我懂
I do.
马赛勒斯
Marcellus.
我觉得我和她…
我们是同一类人
I felt like she and l,
we were kindred spirits.
每一个死去的女孩
会将她的力量释放到下一个女孩身上
Every girl who died,
released her power on to the next.
我是最后一个
所以我拥有了全部的力量
When I was the last one,
I suddenly had all of it.
那些力量本该被释放回大地
All the power that was supposed
to be released back into the earth
以安抚我们的祖先
to appease our ancestors.
这么说收获祭真的起作用了？
So the Harvest was actually working?
在某方面起作用了
我也知道我该被杀死
Something was working, and I knew
that I was supposed to be killed
以完成收获祭
然后我们都会再次重生
so the Harvest could be completed
and we would all be resurrected,
但她们隐瞒了要杀死我们的这个过程
but they lied to us about
how they were killing us.
我怎么知道她们说的重生是不是真的？
How do I know they weren't
lying to us about coming back?
最重要的是，我不想死
But mostly, I just didn't wanna die.
所以我让他救我
So, I let him save me.
马赛尔救了我一命
Marcel saved my life.
好一个英雄救美
You're quite the
knight in shining armor,
但黛维娜一定很清楚你欠她的
不比她欠你的少
though Davina must realize
you owe her as much as she owes you.
如果不是她
你不可能禁止那些女巫使用魔法
You never could have banned the
witches from using magic without her.
她跟女巫们的关系并不好
我是在保护她
She's not exactly besties with them.
I'm protecting her.
不少女巫都想找到她
A lot of them would like
to get their hands on her
然后杀死她好完成收获祭
and kill her to finish the Harvest.
如果不这样，其他女孩就不能复活
而她们将会失去自己的力量
If they don't, the other girls stay dead,
and they lose their power.
如果她们做到了，你将会失去你的统治
And if they do, you lose yours.
黛维娜也会丧命
And Davina loses her life.
真是往日重现啊
Isn't this like old times?
你们两个喝多少了？
Just how drunk are you two?
正在清醒的边缘挣扎着
Skating on the razor's edge.
我去一下洗手间
I'm gonna use the loo.
马上回来
Back in a tick.
20年代后我还没见过他醉成这样
I haven't seen him this
lushy since the twenties.
你是来带他回家的吗
So you came to take him home?
不然我为什么来这里？
Why else would I be here?
我不知道
I don't know.
或许是来确认我不会醉到
不小心说出了我们之间
Maybe to make sure I didn't get too drunk
and spill secrets
不能说的秘密
better left unspilled
about you and me.
我自有分寸
I know better.
但愿如此
I hope so.
因为你不会想跟我作对的
Because you don't wanna
to end up on the wrong side of me.
蕾贝卡米卡森
你也绝对不会想跟我作对的
Rebekah Mikaelson, you do not
wanna be on the wrong side of me.
汤玛斯，是吧？
Tomas, I presume.
马赛尔要我问问你
对于那些死去的巫师你都知道些什么
Marcel asked me to find out what
you know about the dead witches.
我听说他们是为了追杀一个怀孕的狼人
I heard they were going
after some pregnant werewolf.
一个女人独自跑到那种地方真是太傻了
I mean, she was stupid
being out there all alone.
可不是嘛，太傻了
Yeah. She was. Yeah. She is.
有些人真的是很家易上当
It's amazing how gullible
some people can be.
是啊
Yeah.
你可以把这个还给它真正的主人了
You may return this now
to its rightful owner.
已经修好了
It's restored.
我都不知道还会不会再见到他
I don't even know if I'll see him again.
黛维娜，你拥有的力量
是从你死去的朋友那里得来的
Davina, this power that you contain
drawn from your fallen friends,
超过了你的掌控能力
it's too much for you.
你得学会控制
那需要学习和练习
You need control which
requires study and practice.
我的母亲是个非常强大的女巫
And my mother was
a very powerful witch.
她留下了她的魔法书
留下了很多记满咒语的书
She left behind her grimoires,
a legacy of books filled with spells.
那些书里包含了
你可以用来控制魔法的
These books contain all of the tools
that you might need
各种方式
to control your magic.
如果你放我出去
我可以把书拿来给你
If you free me from here,
I can share them with you.
但如果你跟马赛尔离开了
However, if you leave now
with Marcel,
我们将永远见不了面
we'll never see each other again,
我找不到你，也就帮不了你
and I cannot find you,
and I can't help you.
女巫们想操纵我
The witches manipulated me.
你知道她们的下场
You know how that ended.
这不是操纵
This is not manipulation.
这是交换
This is one thing
in exchange for another.
我们来做个交易吧
I'm offering you a deal.
很容易的事情，蕾贝卡
That was fast work, Rebekah.
马赛尔去哪了？
在洗手间补妆吗？
Where's Marcel?
In there touching up his lipstick?
我是有品味的
Credit me with some taste.
那里脏得要命
It's filthy in there.
他去哪了？
Where'd he go?
他没告诉你他走了？
He didn't tell you he was leaving?
没有
No.
你觉得他发现我们在拖延他了吗？
Do you think he
realized we were stalling him?
不
No.
除非他也在拖延我们
Unless he was stalling us.
好了，我们的机会来了
Okay.
Now's our shot.
率备好走了吗？
You ready to blow this joint?
- 等不及了
- 那走吧
-Can't wait.
-All right.
把以利亚留下作为离别赠礼
We'll leave Elijah
behind as a parting gift.
也许他的弟弟妹妹
会因此稍微原谅我
Might buy me a little forgiveness
for pulling one over on his siblings.
走吧
Let's go.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
发生什么事了？
What's happening?
我不知道
I don't know.
(PANTlNG)
感觉不对劲
Something's wrong.
(SCREAMS)
马赛尔，外面有危险
Marcel, there's something
dangerous out there.
带我回去
Take me back.
该死
Damn it.
在这没人能找到你
No one's gonna look for you here.
只是暂时的
直到我带你出城
It's only for a little while
'til I can get you out of town
到安全的地方去
and someplace safe.
现在呢，你要什么我就帮你拿来
For now, I can get
you whatever you want.
你喜欢做些什么？
What do you like to do?
画画
Draw.
还是个艺术家，真不错
An artist, huh?
That's cool.
好的
Okay.
我明天去把文森那边的东西都买来给你
I can buy out Vincent's
for you tomorrow,
再帮你弄些窗帘过来…
maybe get you some curtains or--
马赛尔
Marcel.
你知道我真正想要什么吗？
You know what I really want?
我要她们得到报应
I wanna make them pay.
以利亚？
Elijah?
你能留下我很高兴
I'm pleased you stayed.
你说拿你母亲的魔法书给我还算数吧？
You'll keep your promise
about your mother's spell book?
我会拿来的
I will.
你知道，不管有多难
我珍视我的家人胜过一切
You know, difficulties aside,
I value my family above everything.
你家人辜负了你我很遗憾
I am sorry that yours failed you.
你弟弟克劳斯把你装进棺材
交给了马赛尔
Your brother Klaus handed
you to Marcel in a box,
但你依旧没放弃他
yet you still don't give up on him.
唉，我懒得再放弃了
Well, I've given up on giving up.
这很折磨人
It's an affliction.
我会为我的家人奋战到最后一刻
I will fight for my family
until my last breath.
我也会和女巫们奋战到底
And I'll fight the witches until mine.
现在怎样？
Now what?
你就这么把她留在楼上
随便谁都能找到？
You're just gonna leave her
up there for anybody to find?
我现在没心情，基兰
I'm not in the mood, Kieran.
收获祭过后你就应该带她离开纽奥良
You were supposed to get her out
of New Orleans after the Harvest.
我们已经失去了另外三个女孩
不能再失去她了
We failed those other three girls.
We didn't fail her.
正因如此我才来找你帮忙
我们计划好的
That is why I came to you for help.
That was the plan.
计划有变
Plans change.
特别是你发现她有多强大之后
Especially after you found
out how powerful she was.
我们把话说清楚
Let's get something straight.
你离开的八个月里
我把这地方治理得很好
For eight months since you left,
I've been running this town just fine.
我不需要你回来插手我的事
I don't need you coming back
and getting in my business.
我想干什么就干什么
I will do what I want where I want.
明白吗？
Got it?
你想做老大
You wanna be the boss?
想发号施令吗？
You wanna call the shots?
好啊，但我会联合人类一起拿回掌控权
Fine, but I call the shots
with the humans.
你不会想与我为敌的
And you don't wanna
make an enemy of me.
所以我劝你
离我侄女远点
So, I would suggest one thing,
stay away from my niece.
好啊，那你侄女是谁？
Fine.
Who the hell's your niece?
卡蜜
Cami.
那些人都是因为一个不知是真是假
Those people, all this because
of a vision about my baby
关于我孩子的幻象而死
you don't think is true.
听着，我爱莎宾
Look, I love Sabine,
但她是个非常爱小题大做的女巫
but she's the witch equivalent
of a drama queen.
她说的话看到的东西我都会打些折扣
I've learned to take little stock
in whatever she says or sees.
有时候也希望她能闭上她的嘴
Just kind of wish
she'd kept her mouth shut.
那个收获祭仪式
The Harvest ritual.
你说你不相信
You said you didn't believe in it.
那你猜对了吗？
Were you right?
没有
No.
我亲眼见到了
它发挥作用了
I saw it with my own eyes.
It was working.
那是真的
It was real.
那你怎么能那么肯定
莎宾看到的不是真的呢？
So how can you be so sure
Sabine's vision isn't?
带我外出分散我的注意力？
KLAUS: Taking me on a field trip
to distract me?
既可悲又明显
我可没教你这么差的伎俩
Pathetic and obvious.
I taught you better than that.
你教我保护自己的东西
You taught me to protect what's mine.
你别想把黛维娜从我身边带走，没得谈
You will not take Davina from me.
End of story.
自然界有条亘古不变的真理，马赛尔
An immutable law of nature, Marcel,
就是弱肉强食
is the strong always
take from the weak.
既然你那么强大
那当年你就不需要
If you were so strong, you wouldn't
have run away from New Orleans
狼狈地从纽奥良逃走了
Iike a little bitch
all those years ago.
你带着一群孩子玩游戏
扮国王扮得太久了
You've been playing king with
a bunch of children for too long.
别把我当成你那些夜行者随从，马赛尔
Don't mistake me for one of your
Nightwalker lackies, Marcel.
我随时可以把黛维娜带走
I can take Davina any time I like.
怎么
What the....?
原谅我，马赛尔
Do forgive me, Marcel.
该教训我弟弟的人，是我
But if anyone is to teach
my brother a lesson, it's me.
我不在乎是不是需要拿个链子把你栓住
I don't care if we
have to get you a leash.
你以后再也不许去河口了
That was your last trip to the bayou.
你跟那些狼到底是怎么回事？
What is it with you and
those wolves, anyway?
我觉得我们有着某种联系
I feel like we're connected somehow.
我也不知道
I don't know.
也许这只是我做的一个关于
找到我真正家人的白日梦
Maybe it's just some pipe dream
that I have of finding any real family
但当我感觉全世界都在与我为敌时
out there, but sometimes when
I feel like it's me against the world,
这念头就会支持我走下去
keeps me going.
忘记了
Oh, right.
好吧，如果你问我
家人就如芒刺在背
Well, if you ask me,
family is a pain in the behind.
至于你说的全世界都与你为敌
你怎么能这么说？
And as for being in it alone,
how dare you?
我可不会随随便便为了任何人
I don't ruin a perfectly
fabulous pair of boots
在河口闲逛毁掉我一双好靴子
traipsing through the Bayou
for just anyone.
尼克，总算回来了，你到底…
Nik. Finally. What....?
以利亚
Elijah.
你没事
You're safe.
既然你回家了
第一件事是不是要杀了尼克劳斯？
Now that you're home,
is your first plan to kill Niklaus?
抱歉，稍等我一下
Excuse me, just a moment.
他去哪？
Where's he going?
你回来了
You're back.
我回来了
I'm back.
守不住的承诺就别说
Don't make promises you can't keep.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
我们回到纽奥良的原因
现在看来是个谎言
ELlJAH: Everything that brought
us here to New Orleans was a lie.
苏菲德弗罗捏造了一个
This story that
Sophie Deveraux fabricated,
争夺法语区控制权的故事
this struggle for
control of the French Quarter,
吸血鬼与女巫间的战争
this war between
vampires and witches,
不在于争夺领地
而在于争夺黛维娜
wasn't over territory at all.
This was over Davina.
我发誓我不知道收获祭仪式是真的
I swear I had no idea that the
Harvest could possibly be real.
但你却那么确定我是错的
But the one thing that you were sure of
is that I was wrong and that
我会拿莫妮克的生命开玩笑
现在我的女儿死了
I would risk Monique's life on a
maybe, and now my daughter is dead.
请告诉我我该怎么补救
Please tell me how to fix this.
现在黛维娜在马赛尔手里
我们要怎么做才能找到她呢？
Now that Marcel has Davina,
how are we even supposed to find her?
如果我们不完成仪式
If we don't finish the Harvest,
莫妮克和另外两个女孩就会真的死了
Monique and those two other girls
are dead for real.
看着我
Look at me.
我们会找到方法让莫妮克复活的
You and I are gonna find
a way to get Monique back.
这是我们的秘密
It'll be our little secret.
我们一起去完成
We'll do it together.
我们把墓地封锁起来，不让吸血鬼靠近
We'll seal off the cemetery
from the vampires,
找到黛维娜，阻止马赛尔
然后完成仪式
find Davina, stop Marcel, and finish
the ritual once and for all.
哪怕我要亲自割破黛维娜的喉咙
Even if I have to slit
Davina's throat myself.
八个月前，苏菲德弗罗
和她姊姊简安失去了一切
Eight months ago, Sophie Deveraux and
her sister Jane-Anne lost everything.
四个月之后，一个年轻的孕妇
Now, four months after that,
a young, pregnant girl
走进了她们的餐厅
wanders into their restaurant.
突然间，她们重新燃起了希望
Suddenly, all hope is renewed.
简安真的牺牲了自己的性命
好让她妹妹
Jane-Anne actually sacrificed
her life so that her sister
利用你找回黛维娜
could use you to find Davina.
如果苏菲德弗罗成功找到了黛维娜
If Sophie Deveraux is
successful in capturing Davina,
她就可以让简安的女儿复活
she can return
Jane-Anne's daughter back to life.
我们以为我们是来进行一场权力的战争
We thought we'd come here
to wage a war for power.
但其实这是一场关于家人的战争
This is about family.
为了让她的侄女复活
In order to return her niece to life,
苏菲德弗罗一定会奋战到最后一刻
Sophie Deveraux will fight
to the death.
因此她比任何人都危险
That makes her more
dangerous than anyone.
（简安德弗罗）
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）